交通灯
Traffic 1ight
你先，你上个月人工有五千三百廿六
You made $5320.60 1ast month
还有那么多？
That much 1eft?
你想创了
Of course not
十三张你输了二千四给我
You 1ost $2400 p1aying cards
外围张那儿给我自动转帐，二千三
and $2300 paid to Ah Cheung
伙食费一天二十，上个月三十一日
$20 for food everyday & 31 days 1ast month
即是六百二十，现在剩下六毫
$620 for food than 60 cents 1eft
好过没有
Better than nothing
没零钱，改天再给吧
No changes, 1give it to you 1ater
吴准少
Mocking Face
我生日你折现五百
$500 for my birthday
我老豆死忌折现三百
and $300 for my dad
六百二的伙食费，每个月帮你存千五
$620 for food and save up $1500
剩下一百二十零九，一次过
$120.90 1eft, one for a11
来，预备，预备呀
Get ready
不要呀，我不会的 预备呀
- No, 1don't know how - Get ready
不要呀，我不会的
No, 1don't know how
我变，我变，我变变变
1wanna change
算无数吧
We'11break even
大口发 怎么？
- Big mouth - Yes
你上月的人工是六千四百二十二块二
You made $6422.20 1ast month
六百二的伙食费
$620 for food
你跟你老伙儿两份人情折现八百
$800 for your and your dad's present
你一个月帮我存千五
Save up $1500
还剩三千五百二十二块二，快给
$3522.20 1eft, pay now
不是...
No
我想跟你提一个特惠计划
1propose a specia1p1an
其实你也想存多点钱 对呀
- You want to save up more - Right
我提议你每个月存五千块差不多
1suggest you save $5000.00 month1y
我一向没收你手续费的
1don't charge you for service
几个月仍然没收，而且给你一厘息
1'11give you 1% interest
等你存够一百万
When you have saved up to $1M
我连本带利还给你娶老婆，好吗？
1give it back to you
傻呼呼，不好
Stupid, no
我岳母会帮我蓄的
My mother-in-1aw wi11do it fine
你不同意一定后悔的，不过你不用急
You'11regret
我给三天时间你考虑，想清楚通知我
1give you 3 days to consider
三天？
3 days?
不用了，我结婚不干了
No, 1quit, 1am getting married
《精装追女仔之2》
THE ROMANC1NG STAR 2
这是什么鬼机呀，怎么调不到发达台
Stupid TV, won't tune in
现在是什么台呀？
What's the channe1?
老周电视
Channe19
这个台很差劲
Channe19 is too weak
什么节目都是老板自己出来做
Everything is done by boss
接下来是新闻报告
The news report is next
各位，现在是新闻报告
The news report
昨天最重要的新闻
The opening of Chow's Nood1e Shop
就是老周云吞面铺开张
heads the news
老周云吞面真的非常好吃
Chow's nood1es are tasty
由我老周和我老周电视台的全体艺员
We now have
一齐来剪彩
our grand opening ceremony
多谢...
Thank
难怪收视率那么差
No wonder the rating is so 1ow
找鬼才看呢，吴准少呢
Where is Mocking face
在里面
1n there
光练功有什么用，连胶罐都踩不烂
1t's no use just practicing
这次大件事，我堂侄刘备现在上来
Gee, my nephew is coming up
不用问了，肯定又是借钱
He wants to borrow money from me
屈王之王呀
Mr. Wet
是，我们第一时间收藏起贵重东西
We have to hide everything
雪柜里除了老鼠药之外，什么都别放
We on1y 1eave something toxic in the fridge
还有呀，你记住他向你借什么你都别借
And no matter what he asks, say no
当然了，刘备借荆州一借没回头嘛
Of course no
把东西收起来
Let hide away everything
原来是你呀
Oh, it's you
有没有见贵利王的手下在楼下？
Do you see Wong's pa1s?
那么矮的俊男算不算？
Do you count the boy 1ike this ta11?
不是，快点进去 什么事？
- No, get it - What's up?
你阿叔昨天被贵利王的人打到内伤
Your unc1e got beaten up by Wong
来，快点
Come on
说过省点的，这块腐乳要吃到下个月
This bean curd has to 1ast ti11next month
阿备 阿叔，你发达了
- Pat - You'11be rich unc1e
你来啦
There you come
你说什么，我发达？
What? 1'11be rich?
阿叔昨天去卖血，卖了三百块
1made $300 by se11ing my b1ood
才够还贵利王上个月的一天利息
1t's enough for Wong's 1oan interest for 1 day
不行...
No...
我吐血，我吐血了
1b1eed interna11y
这口血值十几块的，真浪费
1t worths near1y $100
拿来呀
Give it to me
阿叔，你这次一定要相信我
You have to be1ieve me unc1e
我找到一份高尚职业
1have got a job
在老周电视台做助理编导
1am a P.A. at Channe19
九百块一个月
$900 per month
不过，我现在先来向你借五万块
But 1want to borrow $50,000 from you
以后我每月还一百块，还到我死为止
And 1pay you back $100.00 per month ti111die
我越长命，你的收入就越多了
The 1onger 11ive, the more you get
我不便宜他，不便宜他，就是便宜你
1on1y want to benefit you
我不行了
1am
你那么辛苦，我扶你进去休息一会儿
Take a rest
我是不行的了
1can't make it
刘备是我至亲的亲人
But is my next of kin
我死了之后
After my death
一切的身后事交给他就行了
He wi11take care of my everything
你讲得出，做得到才好呀
Do you mean it?
你眼没事，牙没事，肾也没事
Your eyes, teeth, kidney are a1right
全部可以移植给人
They can be transp1anted
我呸
Damn you
你这小子，一世人两叔侄，你那么黑心
How dare you
你一见到我来就扮穷
You a1ways mean to me
我现在的确是
1am poor
借钱没得说，其他的无所谓
No money for you
行，行
A1right
行，我不跟你借钱
1won't borrow your money
跟你借喝，借吃，有厅给我睡就行了
But 1want to stay here
你这小子，行，你听着
OK, but you 1isten to me
吃饭最多挟三次菜，没被子盖别说冻
1have regu1ations on mea1s and bed
冲凉没热水给你用
And no hot showers
电话十块一次，你不要说贵
$10 for every phone ca11
有什么所谓
No prob1em
总之我有瓦遮头就行了，瞌睡会儿
but, 1ike a snap now
我现在换衫去银行拿钱
1am dressing up and then
你两个跟着来保护我
You two escort me to the bank
那臭小子用厕纸，逐格给他好了
We have to be mean to him
是的 逐格给呀
- No prob1em - Mean to him
是
Yes
收买人命呀，谁丢这种东西下来
Shit, wanna take my 1ife
对不起，我们的伙计不小心
1am sorry, it's our fau1t
什么对不起，对不起就行啦，赔钱呀
You have to compensate
但是...
But
但是什么？
But what?
知不知道香港政府规定
Those be1ow 5
矮过五尺的没发言权
have no right to speak
你呀，又矮又麻烦呀你
You are short and troub1esome
戳人家的头好过瘾呀
1t's funny knocking the heads
戳人那么过瘾的
1t's rea11y funny
戳...戳他...
Knock...knock...
兄弟，出来
Come on pa1s
摸骨，按摩
Massage
赔钱是吗？
You want cash?
不是，我意思是支票信用卡都没关系
Not rea11y, 1take cheque & bank cards to
那汤药费怎么收呀？
Do you take medica1charge us we11?
你拿主意
You decide
逢貌丑打三捶
3 b1ows for ug1y
我不算貌丑，我算俊男的
But 1am handsome
对了，俊男打六捶
6 b1ows for handsome
我最恨人戳我的头
1hate being knocked on the head
对不起，老大
1am sorry
我很矮吗，细唛哥？
Am 1short, Sma11Mark?
不是，你简直高大威猛呀
No, you are great
我最恨人家用这种高度来看我了
1hate peop1e 1ook at me that way
那这样行了吗？
What about 1ike this?
那还差不多，不过我还是要打
That's c1ose, but 1have to beat you up
停手呀
Stop
你们不要打架嘛
Stop fighting
不要打...我们大家都是斯文人
Stop fighting, we are gent1emen
打什么架嘛
For what?
是呀，你们快点搬东西上三楼，打架
Right, get the gear up
搬东西啦...
Get moving
你们住三楼呀，我们也是住三楼
You 1ive on the second f1oor
那我们以后同居了
Then we are f1at mates
我们住在B座
We are in b1ock B
我巨蟹座的
1am of Cancer
不要跟他们说话了
Don't ta1k to them
如果被妹姐看到我们跟男人说话
Sister Mui wi11be upset
宝珠，芳芳，家燕 又要挨骂的了
- Po Chi, Fong Fong, Ka Yin - We wi11got b1amed
妹姐
Sister Mui
男人...的确是女人都需要的
Women need men, that's 1ogica1
不过站着也摇摇晃晃的男人你要吧
But those men aren't good enough
我是十三妹，是她们的全权经理人
1'm Sister 13, their manager
有什么跟我说
You can just ta1k to me
这种女人真是茶煲
Damn such woman
你阿妈大减价，优待你老爸
Your dad took advantage of your mum
告诉你不要欺负我们中国同学会的人
You have to respect our members
太像了，太像了
1t 1ooks too fami1iar?
像谁呢？
What fami1iar?
像我年青时纽约一个朋友
He 1ikes my friend in New York when 1was young
你也年青过呀？
When you were young?
还要泡那三个妞
We are interested in the 3 gir1s
有什么好吵的，大家就快做隔壁邻居
Quiet, we are neighbors
那好，不阻你们了，拜拜
A1right, take your time, bye
走啦
Get moving
妹姐
Sister Mui
还不快点搬东西上楼
Get moving
吃薯片，你减到九十八磅没有呀？
Potato Chips? Wait ti11you are 98 1bs
你今晚不要吃饭，你喝水好啦
You on1y have f1uid for your dinner
妹姐，俄们爽楼吧
Sister Mui, 1et's Got up
俄？我呀，俄
Speak proper1y
上楼呀，不是爽楼
Got, get up, not Got up
你今晚不念到三点，你都不要睡
Do work hard on it
你们双生的？我骂她，你又哭
Are you twins?
我看见她们那么惨，我就哭了
No, but 1was emotiona11y moved
我看你练一字马好像V字，我也哭了
Yeah, me too, when 1see the way You practice
还不滚上去
Get up, quick
真的像船头
Damn it, so fami1iar
先生，要什么币？
What wou1d you 1ike?
五千块一百元纸币 千五块十块元纸币，谢谢
$100 notes for $5000 and $10 notes for $1500
谢谢，小姐，五万
$50,000 p1ease
这三个妞真的很正点呀
The 3 Chicks are gorgeous
是呀，三对三，一人泡一个
Yes, one each for us
你就想一人一个，当然是三个我全泡
No, 1want them a11
那个妹姐你们俩分
Sister Mui for the two of you to share
不要动...
Freeze...
小姐，我不要了，你先拿回去
Miss, p1ease take it back
行...你去拿张入数纸再来过吧
Sure, but p1ease fi11in the forms
你们俩听着，不要说我吝啬
You two 1isten to me
明年的工钱现在先发给你们
1pay you sa1aries ti11next year
不要呀，先给他吧...
No, pay him first
拿着...我给了你们了，不关我的事
Take it, it's a11Yours
别动，CID
Freeze, C1D
救命呀
He1p
快点
Quick
让一让
Excuse me
现在是特别新闻报告
Here is a specia1report
市立银行在中午十二点零五分
City Bank was robbed at 12:05 hrs
被三名劫匪入内打劫
by 3 robbers
并遇到一名CID，双方曾经驳火
And C1D was there and they exchanged fire
现在劫匪挟持人质对质
And the robbers are ho1ding hostages
发达台将第一时间向各位报导最新发展
Stay tune and we wi11have instant report
不要呀...
Stay away
你再走过来，我就一枪打死他，别过来
Or 1shoot him down
大哥，小心...小心他们开枪
Sir, be carefu1
香港最后一个男，西门庆来啦
Simon hand is coming
是呀，总监亲自出马，用得着那么夸张
Right, they rea11y take it serious1y
总监
Boss
怎么样，人质打死了没有？
Are the hostages ki11ed?
没有
Not yet
你搞什么？不打死人质有什么好看的
better to ki11the hostage, it 1ooks better
要拍到他这样，收视率才会高的嘛
Stay on him when he fires, better rating
没色情暴力，鬼才看呀
No vio1ence, no porno, no body watch
总监，劫匪似乎想投降
Boss, the betters wanna surrender
什么，投降？
What? Surrender?
别过来，我真的打死他们，我真的打
Stay away or 1'11ki11them
小心
Be carefu1!
你衣服的料子很漂亮嘛
Your shirt is beautifu1
当然了，贵价的
Of course
遮住吧，衰人
You are b1ocking me
最坏就是你，说来打劫这间
1t's your fau1t to rob this bank
回去中环那间珠宝行不就好了
1t's better to rob the shop in centra1
劫了十几次，撤退也容易点嘛
We had done it many times there
别过来
Stay away
救命呀
He1p
干掉他
Ki11them
这肥仔有只烂牙呀
The fatty has a decay
你们已经没有机会
You have no chance
我们伙计已经前后左右包围了你们
The bank is heavi1y surrounded
聪明的就投降
Surrender
不如我们投降吧
Let's surrender
投降？
Surrender?
彭 ！
Bang!
你这臭小子，你几乎累死我了
You bastard, you drag me down
抢我的枪干什么？
Why take my gun?
你那么反骨，我不怕你射我呀
1am afraid that you'11shoot me
给我
Give it back to me
我就不给
1won't
给我枪
Give me back the gun
就是不给
Never
放手呀，放手
Let me go
我发梦而矣，睁开眼就不见了吧
1am on1y dreaming, they are a11gone
幸好找到个好位子
Lucky to have a good sport
没子弹
No bu11ets
干他
Get him
幸好有点暴力镜头
Good, some vio1ence
不要打他，我们要带他回去
Stop hitting him
走...
Get moving
还扮什么？
Stop pretending?
坚叔呢？
Where is Unc1e Ken
在这儿...
1am here...
全走了，他们？
They are a11gone
这不没事了
1t's a1right now
这次你们两个有难了，每人欠我二万八
You owe me $28,000 each
有没有搞错，总共也才五万
1t shou1d be $50,000 in tota1
怎么会二万八呀？
Why $28,000?
你拿了这么半天，不用算利息呀
That's because of interest
你乱算
You made a mistake
请接受我们发达台的访问
We are Channe18, we want to interview you
各位观众，这两位就是今天的英雄
They are the heroes today
两位英雄，你们被劫匪挟持时怕不怕？
Where you scare being he1d hostage
怕？我们刚才那些是演技来的
No, we were acting on1y
拿来欺骗那些劫匪而已
We pretend to deceive the robbers
是呀
Yes
那你呢，发表一下
What about you?
我可不可以点唱啊，我点劲歌金曲
Can 1have my dedication?
我点给烂口发，董董，蚊滋
The song is for Smeary Fat, Tong Tong & Man-chi
和B座的三位靓女听
and the 3 beautifu1in B1ock B
我点谭咏麟那首爱你爱到痹
The Song Crazy Love by A1an
对不起，新闻节目不可以点唱的
Sorry, 1can't have dedications in news report
各位观众，今天特别新闻已报告完毕
The ends our specia1report
走吧...
Get going
你一定是西门庆总监了
You must be Boss Simon Hand
我经常在报纸上见到你
1a1ways read you from newspaper
我叫交通灯
1am Traffic Light
拜拜
Bye
我第一次上电视
1t is my first time
有没有camera face呀？
Do 1have a camera face?
拍照...
Photo...
我们可不可以做艺员呀？
Can we be artists?
可以...可以极了
Of course, of course
那我们明天去找你了
We meet tomorrow then
好...到时再来找我吧
OK, see you 1ater
我样子像白痴吗？随口说说而已
Am 1insane? 1don't mean it
金牌司仪讲过都可以不算数的
We can a1ways deny what we mean
你傻乎乎的
You are stupid
明天七点通告，拍白骨阴阳剑第七集
The ca11time is 7:00 am tomorrow
记住呀，不要迟到
Don't be 1ate
什么，你跳了槽过隔壁？你等等
What? You've joined Channe18
监制，他跳槽了，那现在我们怎么办？
Boss, he's 1eft, what sha11we do?
换人呀
Change the artist
说他练乌龟功练到样子都变了
And change the script as we11
行，那谁改剧本呀？
OK, but who write the script
我？
Me?
我...
1...
发达了，可以偷个懒
Gee, 1can have a break now
进去睡暖一点
1t's warmer inside
真是岂有此理，没理由的
Damn it, how can it be
今天我召开这个紧急会议
The emergency meeting today
就是我们的收视率降到0.03%
1s to remedy our rate of 0.03%
因为隔壁台出了个直播打劫银行节目
Because Channe18 had a 1ive broadcast of bank robbery
还有我们有十个编导，二十个艺员
And 10 of our producers & 20 artists
一天之内全被他们挖了过去
they have 1eft and joined them
发达台财雄势大，我们没法比的
Channe18 has financia1support
混帐，什么叫没法比
So what?
他们用卑鄙，下流，格的手段挖人
They use damn shit ways to get our men
我们老周电视台是讲心的嘛，是...
We ta1k about sense of be1onging
找你的，笙仔
1t's for you, Sam
是，我立即来
Yes, 1'11be right there
这儿不就是在开会
But we are having a meeting here
我去隔壁台开呀，拜拜
1am going to Channe18
你下流，贱格，你走了之后永远别回来
You betrayer, no turning back
我看看还有没有电话来挖我的人过去
Any more phone ca11s from Channe18
岂有此理，你个西门庆
You bustard Simon Hand
我由现在开始，我要进行全力反击
1wi11revenge
谁有本事在发达台能够挖到人过来的
Who can get the peop1e from Channe18
我就连升他三级，人工加他三倍
Promotion by 3 grades and 3 times the sa1aries
我去
1'11go
你是谁？
Who are you?
我知，我知我是很卑微的助理编导
1am a Production Assistant
但是我爱老周电视，我关心它
1care about the Channe19
所以躲在这儿偷听
and 1want to know what's happening
周先生，你放心
Mr. Chow
我帮你挖发达台的人过来
1'11get you peop1e from Channe18
你不要下巴轻轻，你挖谁呀？
Who are you trying to get?
就是今天在直播新闻里
The two hostage
大出风头的两个人质
in the bank robbery
吴准少和交通灯
Mocking face, Traffic Light
你说我明天穿这件去见工，好不好看？
Do 11ook good in this suits for interview
见工？见什么工？
What interview?
你们现在还在打我的工
You are sti11working for me
我们现在正式向你辞职了
We want to quit
辞职？
Quit?
你们够不够义气呀？
Are you pa1?
什么没义气，自从烂口发移民之后
Of course, since Smeary Fat has gone
你的车房没生意了，不如关闭了吧 ！
There is not much business, better c1ose it down
闭不闭是等闲
1t's OK, c1osing it down
但是你们去做明星，不带我去，不对呀
But you shou1d count me in as an artist
我可以做你们经理人的
1can be your manager
我们不是不想，不过你的名太难听
OK but you have to change your name
刘定坚，怎么做经理人呀
Your name doesn't sound good
什么名才不难听呀？
What shou1d be my name?
好像那个叫陈自强就像金牌经理人了
Something 1ike Wi11y
那个陈自强呀，坚强...
Something 1ike Bi11y
我可以叫陈自坚啊
1can be Bi11y Chan
陈自坚？ 比他强大嘛
- Bi11y Chan? - Yes,
不错呀，不过像跟屁虫 坚强
- Not bad - B come before W
隔壁那三个靓仔出来了
They 3 boys are coming out
谁叫我呀？
Who ca11ed me?
是不是呀，我就说他们会冲出来的
See, 1said they wou1d jump out
是呀
Yes
叫我吴准少就好了
1am Mocking Face
我叫交通灯 我叫刘定...
- 1am Traffic Light - 1am Lau Tin...
不是，我...我叫陈自坚
No, 1am Bi11y Chan
是他们俩的经理人
Their manager
我们今天在电视上看见你们了
You were on TV today
以后经常见到了
We wi11a1ways on TV
我们明天去发达电视台签约
We'11join Channe18
你们就好了
That's good
是呀，妹姐也不知要训练我们到何时
Right, don't know how 1ong our training 1ast
训练什么？ 妹姐是我们的经理人
- What training? - Sister Mui is our manager
她要训练宝珠去参加香江小姐选举
She wants Po Chi a compete for Miss Heung Kong
芳芳就参加这一界的超级新人歌唱比赛
& Fong Fong Super New Singer Competition
我们三个还会去试镜拍电视剧
We wi11have the audition
还有K一拍
And "Key 100"
你眼睛不舒服吗？
What's wrong with your eye?
妹姐从来不许我们随便跟男孩交谈
Sister Mui won't 1et us ta1k to boys
好坏啊
That's bad
怎么坏？
How bad?
好...好需要我做个洁身自爱的女孩
She wants us to behave ourse1ves
那洁身自爱，还不回去洗澡
Right and c1ean too
给她搞混了
She spoi1s everything
你们是准备做大明星的
You want to be superstars
隔壁那种小角色，你们也看得上
and the boys are extras on1y
你们签了在我这经理人合约上的
You have signed the contract
写明十二年生约，十二年死约
12 years rigid and 12 years f1exib1e
合约期间不准结婚，不准生孩子
Meantime, no marriage nor birth of chi1d
不准谈恋爱，不准拍拖，不准搞同性恋
No romance and no nothing
不准在街上吃牛杂，你记不记得呀？
No eating in street, remember?
记得的，妹姐
Yes, Sister Mui
好了，当没事发生过
OK, 1'11forget about what happened
我们今天排一排这个得奖的仪态
Let's rehearse the manner
宝珠，你过来，站在这儿
Po Chi, stand here
你们俩都过来站在这儿
The two of you, stand here
一九八八年度香江小姐冠军是...
Miss Heung Kong 1988 is...
七号程宝珠小姐
No.7 Ching Po Chi
我可服了你了
1beg you
表情十足十跟那些评判睡过觉
You 1ook 1ike having affairs with the judges
明知自己第一似的
and sure you wou1d win
你惊喜一下行不行？
You shou1d be surprised
走开，等我示范一下
Let me show you
一九八八年度，香江小姐冠军就是
Miss Heung Kong 1988 is...
八号的十三妹小姐
No.8 Sister 13
十三妹小姐在未来一年将会代表香港
1n the coming year Sister 13 wi11represent
去世界各地做亲善大使
Heung Kong trave1around the wor1d
宣扬香港美好的一面
and show the wor1d the good side of Hong Kong
我们衷心祝福十三妹小姐
We wi11b1ess Sister 13
还笑，要这样才行的嘛
Don't 1augh, you shou1d be 1ike this
过去选衣服，参选那时穿的
Se1ect your costume
这不是走光了
Peop1e can see what's inside
是呀 怎么穿呀？
- Yes - How can 1wear it?
神经病，不走光，鬼才拍你
Do you want to get attention?
这就叫做百密一疏装
1t's good for promotion yourse1f?
还有，一穿低胸那时就当自己驼背
and when you wear the 1ow cuts
一穿夹低的衫就拚命提高双手
Be sure peop1e can see your breasts
一穿短裙那时就把脚抬上桌子
and put your feet on the tab1e having the miniskirt
这样才会有封面做的
When you'11be the gir1on the cover page
那不是很CHEAP
That's too bad
CHEAP，CHEAP不过你穷的
1t's better than poverty
等你过了百万片酬那时
When you get $1M as a cast
就天天去艺术中心溜溜，扮高级
You can act nob1y then
CHEAP不CHEAP用口说的
Low c1ass or not is persona1
你呀，那些急口令念好了没有？
How is your recitation?
好难背的，妹姐
1t's very hard
有什么难
1t is not
大妈执到个瓜，细妈拿着束花
Me1on on the ground, f1ower on the ground
大妈赞细妈的花，细妈要大妈的瓜
Me1on and f1ower are 1ying on the ground
楼上猛在弹结他
Music from guitar
大妈拿起了瓜，细妈带上束花
Picking up the me1on and f1ower
一齐去找那音乐家
then go to 1ook for a star
大妈插好束花，细妈吃了那瓜
Hard to choose from so many stars
陪那音乐家，大家一起弹结他
End up without any star
大妈，细妈，弹结他...
Me1on, f1ower, guitar
你呀你练不好今晚不要吃饭啊
work hard on it nor no food for you
你的一字马练得怎么样？
What about your exercise?
你跟宝珠下去买饭盒，今晚不煮饭
Go to buy some take-away
是不是真的？
1s it true?
不要骗我啊
Don't cheat me
干什么呀你？
What are you doing?
就这样，不说那么多了，挂线吧
We ta1k 1ater, bye
再讲贞操亦难保呀
Watch out
讲完没有呀？
Have you finished?
拿一块来
Give me a do11ar
吴准少先生在吗？
1s Mocking Face in?
我是，什么事？
1am, what's matter?
我是老周电视的 总经理助理Mr. Wen Bad-chi
1am Mr. Wen Bad Chi from Channe19
我现在派监制刘备先生去你那儿
the producer Mr. Lau is going to you
你等等他，好吗？
P1ease wait for him?
不用客气，我们明天签发达电视台了
1wi11sign up for Channe18 tomorrow
叫他省省口水吧
He doesn't have to come
什么？你签发达电视台？
What? You sign up for Channe18?
这个电视台真的有型
This station 1ooks great
不知怎么找西门庆呢？
How can we find Simon Hand?
不用你烦，找人去通传一下
Ask the office boy
是呀 那你还不去
- Yes - Don't just stand here
你是我们经理人，去吧
You are the manager
谢谢，小姐 什么事呢？
- Excuse me, Miss - Yes
我和两位艺员约了西门庆先生签约
We have an appointment with Mr. Simon Hand
麻烦你等等
P1ease wait
他回来了，怎么样？
How is it?
三十八楼
38/F
三十八楼那么高呀？不去了
38/F, so high
去死吧，走呀 搅什么？
- Non-sense, get moving - What's matter with you?
你们先上去，我一会儿来
You go first, 1come 1ater
快点，那不是谭咏麟吗，做了大闸蟹呀
That's A1an Tam
潮声，浪声，去...
The natura1sound
NEXT
我现在要唱一首灰色
1'11sing a song "Gray Co1our"
Music
“灰色” ...
The Co1our grey
Next
我现在唱一首阳光大减价
1'11sing a song P1enty of Sunshine
Mr.黎，COME BY WA 这个叮钟很漂亮
Mr. Lai, that's good
我是日本超级唱片的代表
1am from Nippon Supper Record
什么唱片公司？
What so?
SUPER MUSIC RECORD
SUPER MUS1C RECORD
我来香港找新人，这个VERY GOOD
1am 1ooking for singers
这个？
That one?
她去日本，可以红过中森明菜的
She'11be a super star in Japan
凭她？
Her?
好极了
Good
小姐，我的咭片
Miss, my card
我们日本公司要签你，你快退出比赛
We'11sign you up
你不要乱说，她已经进了决赛
She is in the Fina1
你不要乱找人
Mind what you are doing
我真的进了决赛
1am in the Fina1?
是呀，你签了同意书，不可以退出的
Right, you can't drop out
真是可惜，可惜了
That's too bad
快走，赶他出去
Get him out
不要浪费了，不要赶我呀
Don't get me out of here
我会出好多钱跟你打官司，毁了约吧
1'11pay for the court changes
神经病
1nsane
小姐...
Miss...
经理人说的
The manager says
小姐，我们约了西门庆先生
We have an appointment with Mr. Simon Hand
总监和董事长在开会
He is in a meeting
有什么事？
What's matter?
有位吴准少先生和陈自坚先生找你
A Mr. Face and Mr. Chan want to see you
什么人呀？我和亚SIR正在练气功
Who are they?
告诉他，叫他等一会儿
Ask them to wait
亚SIR，我整套打完了
Sir, 1have finished
怎么样，西门庆，觉不觉得有条气在这
How do you fee1Simon?
觉得...简直有条气团团转
1fee1the air trave1ing everywhere
不是吧，难道你打通了任督二脉
Rea11y? You have reached a higher 1eve1
我都没到那境界
Even 1haven't reached that 1eve1yet
那一定不是，一定是我搞错了
We11, 1think 1did it wrong
我的气功已经可以发出体外
1can pass the air outside my body
那么奇？ 不信你试试
- So strange? - You try?
你感不感觉得到我的气？
Can you fee1my air?
觉呀...好大条气呀
Yes, it's a big current
是不是热热的
1s it a bit hot?
简直全身都热了
1t's hot a11over the body
亚SIR，我被你的气功弹开了
Sir, 1got bounced by your current
你好厉害，厉害...
That's strong
所以我八十几岁人身体还那么健康
That's why 1am sti11hea1thy at my 80' age
我除了练气功，还学了点穴呢
1know how to tack1e the nerves
那么厉害？
Rea11y?
你不相信吧？
1know you won't be1ieve
点点儿吧
So and so
亚SIR，我不会动了，你真点了我穴道
Sir, did you tack1e me? 1can't move
这个叫做玄机穴
1t's ca11ed Yin Kei Nerve
我可以点你的哭穴，笑穴和死穴
1can tack1e your cry, 1augh and dead nerve
那你不是很厉害了
You are rea1great then
试试点你的笑穴
Try your Laugh nerve
你做什么？
What are you doing?
你点了我笑穴了
You had tack1ed my 1augh nerve
我都还没点
1haven't yet
你的气功厉害嘛，第二样呀
You are good at you See Kung try another
我点你的哭穴
1'11get your cry nerve
亚SIR，快点帮我解穴
Sir, re1ease me, quick
亚SIR，你真的好厉害
Sir, you are powerfu1
古灵精怪，拿着
Don't foo1around, ho1d it
扮鬼扮马
1am not kidding
我一定要找两个我不认识的外人
1'11get someone 1don't know
来试试我的功力
and test my power
行...我叫亚赐和亚弟上来
OK, 1'11send Chi and Dai up
不行，那些是你的手下，当然是帮你
No, they work for you, 1can't rea11y test
这两个我不认识的，正合道
These two are perfect
你们俩进来
Come in, the two of you
起身，走
Let's go
来...进来...
Come in...
西门总监
Boss Simon
亚SIR，这是无关的人
Sir, they are on-1ookers on1y
就是不认识的才好
That wi11do fine
那好吧，你等等，我跟他先说一句
1take to him first
你们走来干什么？
What are you here for?
你说签我们做艺员的嘛
You wanted as to be artists
我是他们经理人
1am their manager
那，那好吧，签你们也行
OK, 1'11sign you up
你们先让亚SIR练点穴
But you are a dummy for him to practice
他点你们笑穴，你们就笑
You 1augh when he tack1es your 1augh nerve
他点你们哭穴，你就哭，明白没有？
You cry when he tack1es your cry nerve
那这不叫点穴了，是耍他呀
But that's not nerve tack1ing
对呀
Right
这就叫做演技
That's acting
亚SIR，他们明白了
Sir, they thorough1y understand
我明...
1understand
亚SIR...
Sir...
好，那我来啦
OK, 1'11try
先点你的哭穴
Your cry nerve
哭穴呀，干嘛你呀呀声的
Cry nerve, who do you ye11?
痛的嘛
1t's painfu1
现在才哭，你怎么那么迟钝
Are you menta11y retarded?
不要啦，我点他的笑穴
1'11try the 1augh nerve
对不起，亚SIR
Excuse me, Sir
你集团那边叫你开紧急会议
phone ca11for you
行了
OK
西门，你照这本书帮他们解穴
Simon, re1ease them according to the instruction
亚SIR，你慢慢走
Sir, you are terrific
你不要走
You stay
都走了，你还笑 我也不想
- Don't have to 1augh now - 1try not to
不准笑
Stop 1aughing
你以为我想呀，我停不了呀
1can't he1p it
是不是真的被他点了穴呀
Were you rea11y tack1ed by him
不是吧
1don't think so
有解穴方法
There is a so1ution
劳烦你
P1ease
不行...我没命了
No, 1'11die
唯有带你去
Bring you to him is the on1y way
快点找那老家伙
Get the o1d man
警卫室
Security
给我赶那两个疯子走，他们正要下来了
Send the two maniacs away, they are coming
我立即去
1wi11
不见那老家伙
Where is the o1d man?
靓女呢
Beauties
这可不是办法，先去洗个脸，去啦
Let's fresh up, first
死了，不行呀
See, can't stop
你这样忍也不行的
We have to find the so1ution
不如想你的伤心事，想想你老爸老妈
Think of your terrib1e past
怎么想，我老爸老妈从小捡我回来
My past was too good
天天打我，他死了我拿了二百万遗产
1got $2 M from my parents
那想想和女朋友分手，很痛苦，很痛苦
Think of your ex-gir1friend
不行呀，我和我女朋友分手的时候
That's nothing bad worth mentioning
屈了她廿万分手费，都不知多happy
1got $200,000 from her when we broke off
你真够麻烦的
You are so troub1es one
我出去帮你找医生，你不要动呀
Stay here, 1get a doctor for you
你站住好了
Stand here
你怎么这样，射了我一裤子...都是
Watch out, you wet my pants
你笑什么？
What are you 1aughing at?
不是呀
No
阿妈生出来的嘛
That's given by birth
不是
No
你好厉害吗？
Are you a giant?
你快给我消失
Get 1oss quick
连牙都笑掉了
1t's funny
那个疯子在那边
The crazy man is over there
各位，龙哥生前带领兄弟们雄霸喜剧界
Brother Lung was prominent in our fie1d
现在他不辛从三十八楼跌下来死了
And now he fe11from 38/F
大家都很悲痛
And we a11fee1sad
龙哥一生对兄弟照顾，对子女负责任
Brother Lung cared about us a11
笑什么？
Don't 1augh
什么呀，我笑你们误解了龙哥
You don't understand him
有什么理由要哭，龙哥不想我们哭的
He doesn't want us to cry
龙哥是想我们笑
He want us to 1augh
你不会说，等我来说
Let me give the speech
各位，其实龙哥生前将欢笑送给大家
We11, Brother Lung gave us happiness
他死了之后也希望大家继续笑
and he wants us to be happy
龙哥绝对不希望大家不开心
He wants us to fee1good
所以我们要化悲愤为欢笑
and so we shou1d keep on 1aughing
我们要继续把龙哥将欢笑 送给观众的精神
We have to keep up his spirit
来，我们现在一起为龙哥大笑十五秒
Let's 1augh for him for 15 seconds
好...还是你最了解龙哥
Great, you rea11y understand him
龙哥没得顶呀
Long 1ive Brother Lung
今晚我们为龙哥去福临门开个大吃会
Let's have a gourmet tonight
乳猪鲍翅席，每人二百块，不够我包了
Set mea1, $200 each, 1pay the difference
你们去到那儿找林过云一定能搞妥的
Ask for KW Lam there, he'11fix it up
就是他
That's him
你不要推我，我忍你...
Don't push me, 1can't get patient...
有没有搞错，你干嘛扔我出来呀？
What's going on?
全让你恶呀
Don't have to be crue1
你没事吧
Are you a1right?
是呀，摔一摔没事了，解了穴道了
Oh, that fa11cured me
交通灯呢？
Where is Traffic Light?
他可好，不用被人扔出来
No, didn't get thrown out
交通灯...怎么样？
How are you Traffic Light?
我要报仇
1wanna revenge
打倒发达台
Channe19 gets on top on Channe18
好...
Good
这次真让你害死了
1have to b1ame you this time
年青人
Hey, guy
你不是说能请吴准少和交通灯过来吗
did you get Mocking Face & Traffic Light
现在人呢？
Where are they?
哭什么？ 周先生
- Why do you cry? - Mr. Chow,
吴准少他得了爱滋病
Mocking Face has got A1DS
交通灯更惨，得了血癌
And Traffic Light has b1ood cancer
他们说时日无多，不想做艺员了
They don't want to be artists anymore
那他们岂不是只有一个月的命？
Do they have one month 1eft?
是呀 还不快点请他们来
- Yes - Then sign them up
做完一个月之后我不用给工钱他们呀
We don't have to pay them
你真没用，炒你的鱿鱼
You are use1ess, you are fired
刘备，我们决定帮你
Mr. Lau, we wi11join you
你是吴准少还是交通灯？
You are Mocking Face or Traffic Light?
我...我当然是吴准少
1am Mocking Face
我还是搂着他好点
1better embrace him
搂我呀？
Me?
欢迎...
We1come
干什么？
What are you doing?
我们走啦，人家炒我鱿鱼了，走吧
1am 1eaving, 1am fired
你误会了
1t was a misunderstanding
我没误会 我不是这意思
- 1wasn't - 1didn't mean it
你知我几十岁整天都会讲错话的
You know that 1don't mean what 1say
炒你鱿鱼就是升你做监制
To fire you means to upgrade you
你真棒呀
Thank you
我听人说监制的人工有九千块一个月
Producers get $9000 per month
最多千二
No, $1200
你又说错，我知你想说九千二是不是？
1know you mean $9200?
不是，是一千二
No, $1200
听着呀，其实他想说一万二的 是不是？
Right, you mean $12000?
差那么远
What a difference
不要听说了
Don't 1isten to him
九千打个九折，好了吧？
$9000 1ess 10%, OK?
你们合作做节目吧
You work together on the same program
好啊，什么节目呢？
Good, what program?
大哥讲话你要听
The hosts of Do what you were to1d?
交通灯先生，吴准少先生
Mr. Traffic Light & Mr. Mocking Face
各位观众，大哥讲话你要听这个节目
Hi, we begin the program
现在开始
Do what you were to1d?
我们今晚的特别嘉宾就是著名议员
Our specia1guest tonight is counci1of
司徒铭先生
C. To Ming
你们这个节目的意识很不良
Your program is bad tasted
我会通知有关方面检讨一下
1'11ask for consu1tation
现在我开始讲今晚的稿题就是...
My topic for tonight is...
请
P1ease
不要问，只要信
No queries, just be1ief
不要问我那么多，信我，投我一票
Trust me, vote for me
我会帮大家搞妥
1'11take care of you
等大家得到繁荣，安定，发达
1assure you of prosperity & wea1thiness
不过议员... Shut up
- but counci1or... - Shut up,
几时轮到你发言呀
you have to right to speak
这个社会是要我为你们去争取
1'11fight for your rights
你们什么都不用想
You don't need to consider
到时投我一票，我帮你们搞妥
Vote for me, 1take care of you
那你为大家争取什么呢
What wi11you fight for us
现在我说还是你说呀
1do the ta1king?
就是民主，推进点...我这边脸上镜点
Light for democracy, this side of my face
看不见他们俩都不要紧
Just my c1ose up
谁讲都不用听
Don't 1isten to others
听我讲就行了，我说什么就什么
Just 1isten to me
这怎叫民主呀
He ca11s that democracy
你还插嘴我要反映给广播事业委员会
You shut up, or 1'11fi1e a report
封你们电视台
And c1ose down your station
你们的节目教坏小孩子
Your program is bad for kids
我早就说要打压你们 这些不良电视，电影的
And 1had said to stop bad movie and TV
踩死我们行不行呀？
Do you think you can?
不行？抓你坐监都行的
Of course, 1can put you in jai1
你俩个不良的节目主持人
You are worst hosts
不良吧
Worst
你们敢打我？
You dare to hit me?
封你们的台
1'11c1ose down your station
不要封我们的台，我们没得混了
P1ease don't c1ose down our station
别动手，你们下等人，没资格跟我说话
We'11get 1aid off?
打他呀...
You bastard
Bent him up
糟了
Oh, my god
不要打...
Stop fighting
现在嘉宾和主持打成一片
The guest and the hosts are having a good
这次真麻烦了
We are rea11y in troub1e
你们看看，我收到那么多告票
See how many summons 1have got
那个司徒铭告到我没命，你们说怎办？
That C To Ming comp1ains a 1ot
我...
1...
打什么，讲就由他们讲啦
You shou1d 1et him speak
打什么呀
Why beat him
是呀...都是你们这班人不对
Right...you were wrong
你就很好吗？
You are not much better
没商量，全炒了你们鱿鱼
You are fired, a11of you
走就走吧
OK, we wi111eave
走呀...走迟点打跛你的脚
Hurry up, or 1break your 1egs
摔死你的，周先生哦
They deserve it, Mr. Chow
哦什么，你也走吧 我也走？
- You have to 1eave too - Me too?
走迟点信不信我打跛你两只脚
Hurry up, or 1break both your 1egs
打到你残废为止
Turn you into a handicap
周先生，好消息呀
Good news Mr. Chow
我们的收视率本来平均得0.03%
Our rating was 0.03%
但是昨天的节目大哥讲话你要听
But yesterday's Do what you were to1d
后半截播出到打人那个时段
The rating of the second ha1f
升到百分之四十呀
Raised up to 40%
快点叫他们回来
Ask them to come back
不对就要打节目主持人
Mr. Face and Mr. Light, hosts
吴准少，交通灯先生
Of Okay or to be hit
各位观众，今天我们不对就要打节目
Hi, our Okay or to be hit
请到的特别嘉宾
Has a specia1guest
这家伙就是，有名的色鬼，曾公子
He is Mr. Tsang, the maniac
你不是这么介绍我吧
1s that how you introduce me?
不是事必要你讲
You don't rea11y have to ta1k
你所讲的每一句话立即播出街，坐下
But it is 1ive broadcast, sit down
坐呀
Sit
我现在郑重声明我只是风流不是色鬼
1c1ean it, 1foo1around, but not maniac
流你老爸，每次选美会你都去
You are a1ways at the beauty pageants
你去干什么，参选吗？
What are you there for?
小心我告得你们台倒闭
Mind that 1'11fi1e a comp1ain
不告我们也都要倒闭啦
By a11means
庙街有首小调讥讽你
There is pop song about you
曾公子，曾公子，泡妞快过掉眼屎
Mr. Tseng, Mr. Tseng
花柳生到落张椅
A1DS a11over the body
我现在拒绝说话
1refuse to ta1k
让我帮你说了吧
Let me ta1k for you
你干嘛要抢人家离婚老婆？
Why you a1ways court divorced 1adies?
你干嘛专门要仔不要母？
You on1y take the kid but not the mum?
你们俩够了啊
That's enough
干嘛甩掉了一个又一个？
Why do you 1eave one after another?
你刚才拒绝说话，现在不准你说话
You can't ta1k anymore now
你以为我不知道，连家里的菲佣都泡
You are interested in a11age...
女孩们都泡光了，那我们泡什么？
1nc1uding young and o1d
干嘛整天看黄色书？
And you read porno magazines?
干嘛你心口这儿有毛？
And hair on your chest?
干嘛你长那么高？干嘛你不穿内裤？
And you are so ta11?
干嘛你不去天天渔港吃饭？
And enjoying yourse1f?
没去天天渔港吃饭都要打
You wi11get beaten up if you don't go there
还拖椅子来
You get the chair
救命...
He1p...
妈的 打我错啊
- Go to he11 - Hit are wrong!
Sorry
好...谢谢
Good...thanks
把香槟先收起来，我们有情饮水饱嘛
Let's keep the Champaign
来，为庆祝我们的收视率超过51%
Let toast to ce1ebrate
大家来干杯，干杯
our 51% rating
干杯
Cheers
周先生，今次糟了
Mr. Chow, it's bad news
收视率百分之五十，还糟了
What bad news?
就是因为我们上次赢了隔壁台
Because of our 1ast victory
亚SIR好生气
Mr. Chow is angry
出齐全台人马抢拍风流侠盗楚天香
They are shooting one of our stories
三天拍好了
They finish it in 3 days
那怎么办？真是卑鄙无耻呀
They are barbarians
周先生不用怕
Don't worry Mr. Chow
他们拍侠盗，我们一样可以拍
We shoot the same thing
还要比他快播出
and broadcast tomorrow
一定要比他们快
We wi11be the first
你拍什么呀？
What are you going to shoot?
楚婆香
Chu Fai Heung
刘备
Lau Pai
还不去化妆
Get ready, put on your make up
时候还早，上来看看控制室
P1enty of time, 1et's 1ook at the contro1room
我什么机械都会弄的 刘监制
- 1can fix any machine - Mr. Lau,
特别效果电脑坏了
the effect computer is broken
叫工程部去修呀
Ask the technician to fix it
婆王的老婆生孩子，走了
But he has gone
那部电脑有什么用？
What's the computer for?
定格，快镜，慢镜，倒带，出字幕
Sti11, fast forward, s1ow motion...
那怎么办？ 别担心
- What sha11we do? - Don't worry,
有一流大师傅在这，等我看看
1et me have a 1ook
Easy job啦，有没有钳子
Easy, get me the p1iers
迟早弄坏了
You wi11damage it
不是呀，他好像有两下子呀
He 1ooks 1ike working on it
玩完了
1t's over
怎么跟车子的机器不同
1t's different from motors
那现在怎么办呀？
Then, what now?
即是说什么特别效果都没有了
No more effects
出字幕
Caption
主题曲
Theme song
湖海洗我胸襟，河山飘我影踪
My sight is everywhere in mother nature
不要移走，看不到歌词了
Don't move, 1can't read the 1yrics
影踪...
The trace
唱呀...
Sing
卡带了？
Something wrong with the tape?
是呀
Yes
快点拿过来
Bring it over
云彩挥去却不去，人生休说苦痛
We can't evade what we don't 1ike
我楚婆香约了十大高手在这比武的
1shou1d have 10 counter-parts
怎么人影都没有呢？
But no one in sight?
冷气跑掉了，把门关上
C1ose the door
高手呢？
Where are my counter-parts
监制呀，那班武师说不加人工，不干了
Mr. Lau, the stuntmen want pay rise
先拍完吧
Wait ti11me finish
没钱没得拍
No money, no shooting
叫交通灯一个人顶住呀
Ask Traffic Light to carry on
就出来了
They are coming
奇怪了，那班高手还没到呀？
Where are my counter-parts
没理由，难道他们去错了少林寺
They shou1dn't make any mistakes
十大高手到了
1am 10 counter-parts
你是十大高手？ 当然
- You are? - Yes
Let me take a look
Let me take a 1ook
我名就叫做十大高手啦
My name is 10 counter-parts
好，你是找我比剑的，你是哪儿的？
Good, where do you be1ong?
你问我是哪儿的？
Where do 1be1ong?
道...道...道弥敦道，广东道
1be1ong to here
漆咸道，干诺道，谢斐道
There and everywhere
绿波三度，黑波七度，off扣四度
1be1ong to the nature
道亦有道，我自行我道
1am what 1am
这种打斗要用慢镜头才好看的
S1ow motion for these shots
‎（慢动作）
(S1ow Motion)
慢镜头还是不好看，要快镜才行
No, we shou1d speed it up
不错呀
Not bad
快镜 快...快镜头
- Speed it up - Faster
‎（快动作）
(Quick Motion)
这样才够刺激的
That's exciting
你干什么，这么压下来怎么行呀
Why do you 1ie on top of me?
我没力气了 没力气，斗法术吧
- 1have no more strength - Let's try magic
想不到我出剪，你却出锤
1cut out scissors and you are the hammer
我被你锤子所伤
You hurt me with the hammer
我去找我师父花和尚来对付你，收剪
1ask my master it dea1with you
我收锤
1wi11wait
吊高他 不行...
- Pu11him up - No...
不要把我拉那么高，放低点
Can't get me too high
还是不够高 是呀，不够高
- Not high enough - Right, not high enough
高点...
Higher...
发达台那边正在拍出浴镜头
Channe19 is shooting a shower scene
过去看下
Let go to take a 1ook
放我下来，你这班死色鬼
Re1ease me, you maniac
快些看戏，找个好位置
Get a good position to see
我们无论如何都不拍的 是呀
- We won't agree - Yes
大姐呀，现在剧情需要
But it is in the script
大香香公主和小香香公主在这里出浴
Tai watches the 2 princess
让戴家乐看到
in bathing
剧情说在湖面上的，现在只有一个盆
1t's in a 1ake in the script
找不到湖就找个盆下水啦
We have to use the basin instead
来，脱衣服
Get undressed
你现在是骗我不懂呀
You try to deceive me?
电视台怎么可以出这么暴露的镜头
TV can't have such shots
你们这些小姐真麻烦
Just do what you are to1d
他们俩都不肯拍，那怎么办？
They don't want to do it
不行，西门总监order拍来自己看的
Boss Simon wants the shots persona1
一定要拍的
We have to shoot it
这样呀
And
现在你们俩个不肯拍
Do you agree to shoot or not?
今天一切损失由你们俩负责
Or you pay for today's expenses
你现在算是欺人么，你们不用怕他的
Don't be afraid of them
老老实实，有没有签约
Frank1y, any contracts
是呀 没有
- Right - No
没有就不用怕
Then, don't have to worry
不要再逼她了
Don't force them
再逼她，报警说你们非礼的
Or 1ca11the po1ice
怎么办？
So?
好，现在我们收工，你们自己走回市区
We wrap now, you wa1k back home
不用怕，我们载你出去
We give you a ride
辛好有你们
Lucky to have you here
你们有事，我们当然帮的
We are a1ways around to he1p
我们初入电视台也是为了泡你们嘛
And we wanna, friend1y with you
不是，我们想邂逅你们
We wanna make friends
真的很谢谢你
Thanks
不用
No
我们在电话亭见过的
We met at the phone box
我叫刘备，是老周电视台的监制
1am Lau Pai, Ex. Producer of Channe19
你呢？ 我叫宝珠
- And you? - 1am Po Chi
宝珠呀，你们不用怕的
Don't worry, Po Chi
像你这种样貌气质
Someone 1ike you
我们老周电视的大门随时为你打开
Channe19 wi11a1ways we1come
多谢 不用多谢
- Thanks - Don't mention it
你们俩个衰仔，重色轻友
You bastards
靓女，你们也在这儿呀
Gir1s, Hi
家燕呢？ 她在拍第二个剧
- Where is Ka Yin? - She's working on another p1ay
难怪了 相请不如偶遇
- No wonder - Let's join together
我们不如改天一起玩
sometime
好呀...不过要叫家燕
Good, and Ka Yin has to come too
可以这样出来晒半天太阳，真舒服呀
How nice to enjoy the sun
如果你欢喜，我天天都可以陪你晒的
1can be with you a11day if you 1ike
你以为天天都那么好运呀
1t's not a1ways 1ucky 1ike today
今天妹姐去了大屿山吃斋
Sister Mui has gone to Lau Tau today
我们才有得偷懒
So we are free today
那个妹姐看得我们很牢，寸步难行的
As Sister Mui watched us very tight
日常那有这么好运的
Otherwise, we can't have time to enjoy
没理由，十三妹管得你们太严了
Sister Mui is too tyrannous
简直心理变态，那有不让人拍拖的
She is a maniac
我看对付这种女人最好找个男人给她
We better find her a boy friend
等她尝到爱情的滋味，冰山也变火山
So she can enjoy 1ife
那就是要找人将冰山劈开
Teach her to enjoy 1ife
是呀，劈开她啦
Yes, enjoy 1ife
谁肯捱义气呀？
Who wi11teach her?
是呀，有谁肯呀？
Right, who wi11vo1unteers?
他！他 ！
Him
This is a man！This is a pan ！
This is a man! This is a pan!
A man and apan ！
A man and a pan!
如果你要了这个man
1f you take this man
就一辈子拿住这个pan-pan
You are over
女人漂亮不了多久的
Beauty doesn't 1ast 1ong
有几个好像我跟青霞这样的
There are not many examp1e 1ike me
所以说，女人的青春要留给自己
And be sure to enjoy your beauty
不要留给那些坏男人
Don't 1eft the man take advantage
刘备
Lau Pai
宝珠
Po Chi
妹姐 你来做什么？
- Sister Mui - Why are you here?
你们三个进去，省得让人看便宜了
Get inside a11of you
做什么？
What do you want to do?
没有，我本来也不敢来找你的
We11, 1was not coming to see you
但是我实在忍不住
But 1just can't he1p it
想找我三个靓女去你那三流电视台
You want my 3 beauties to Channe19
你想也不用想
Forget it
我已经跟西门庆总监建立了良好关系
Simon and 1have good re1ation
她们做定发达台的花旦了
They wi11join Channe18
不是，你听我说，我是来找你的
Listen, 1come to see you
找不到成龙，洪金宝
Get Jackie and Samo's master
就找他师父于占元
to substitute
是呀
Right
不是，找不到小彬彬，就找小彬彬姐姐
No, get Bun's sister if Bun is not there
你听我说，是我阿叔刘定坚呀
Listen, my unc1e Lau Tin Kin
你是说常叫我茶煲那个呀？
The one used to ca11me teapot?
就是呀，他自从见过你之后
Yes, after he has met you
朝思暮想，茶饭不思，暗恋你啊
He can't he1p thinking of you
你乱讲
Mind your words
不是呀，有事实为证的
Trust me, we have proof
来，你不信跟我过去看看，去吧
Come, take a 1ook yourse1f
从今以后working hard
1have to start working hard
拿了金咭，拿绿咭
After the go1d card, then the green card
学完英文学日文，以后不再玩女人
Learning Eng1ish and Japanese, no more foo1around
每日洗澡和擦牙，去买生发水回来擦
And get c1ean and fresh everyday
戒烟，戒酒，戒赌钱，入院...
Give up my bad habits
飞掉风骚娘，船头爱茶煲
And on1y 1ove Tea-pot
有个叫风骚娘的吗？
He has another gir1friend?
有，不过一见到你之后就甩掉了她了
Yes, but he 1eft her after seeing you
做什么，甩了她也生气呀
Why are you upset
关我什么事呀
1am not
不过你猜世上有没有藕断丝连的呢？
But wi11they sti11keep in touch
我就说没有
1don't think so
你不信？来，过来看看
Come, have a 1ook
来，看看，看着呀
Have a 1ook yourse1f
看着呀
Have a 1ook
有什么好看的？
Why?
不要眨眼呀
Watch it c1ose1y
我爱茶煲
11ove Tea-pot
相信了吧
Are you be1ieve?
相信吧
You be1ieve
冤孽也要出去谈一会儿嘛
Don't be shy, ta1k at over
肯定是那班臭小子作弄我
Those bastards
岂有此理，作弄完一次又一次
a1ways trap me
你吃剩那么多早餐？
Left-over for me?
男人要补一下的
You need more nutrient
请尊重点好不好？
Wi11you respective?
我现在不尊重你吗？
1do respect you?
尊重我，就不要摸手摸脚，孤男寡女
Then don't touch me
怕什么呀，这儿又没有人
There's no one around
坚叔 有呀，谁说没有
- Unc1e Ken - Yes,
立即就有给你看
someone is around
这家伙好厉害，她想侵犯我
She wants to assau1t me
进去再说
Let's ta1k inside
什么？
What?
我们要你泡她？
We want you to date her
什么？我泡她，有什么理由？
Date her? What reason?
你不泡她，我们怎么追家燕 宝珠，芳芳
Then we can date Ka Yin, Po Chi, Fong Fong
对呀
Right
好吃的你们吃，难吃的我吃，不行
You a1ways 1eave me the rubbish
不行？我们换经理人
You object? We change the manager
是呀
Yes
好，泡她也行，给我钱
OK, but give me money
又要钱 就这样，我洗澡
- A1ways money - Time's up, 1need a shower
船头
Shu Tau
说什么呀？什么船头，船尾的
What did you say?
去那儿呀？
Where are we going?
还用说，这时候当然是先医肚子，走吧
Of course to get some food
在...在这儿吃呀？
To here?
不好看，看什么，想想吃什么
Just think what to have
哥哥
Excuse me
哥哥，吃点什么？
What wou1d you 1ike?
看她吃什么？
See what she eat?
随便吧
Anything
给她一份蛋治
Egg sandwich for her
一只蛋？两只蛋？
One or two eggs?
当然是一只，吃多了有胆固醇的
One is enough
单春蛋治一份
One egg sandwich
坚哥，你呢？
What wou1d you 1ike?
我，鸭腿汤饭，切多半只烧鹅来
Rice with soup and ha1f a duck
好的
Okay
别太开心，我自己吃的
1t's just for myse1f
不要紧，人家好久没吃过单春蛋治了
1t's OK, when did you 1ast have
自坚
egg sandwich
有没有弄错，两个加起来一百多岁
Oh, they are very o1d
还谈情说爱
but sti11ta1king 1ove
叫你别看的，省得麻烦
Stop staring
怕什么呀
1don't care
我男朋友是中国同学会会长
My boy friend is of the Chinese gui1d
敢不敢跟他打
Dare you fight with him
是吗？
Rea11y?
不是，别听她说
No, she is bu11shitting
我是中国城同志会的会长才对
1am Chairman of the China Town
你怕什么呀，自坚
Why are you scared, Chi Kin
这班臭小子那是你的对手
They are on1y rubbish
动手 不要打
- Fix him up - Stop fighting
你们打船头
You beat him
何止打他，连你也要打
Yes, we beat you up too
死八婆，动我大佬
Damn you, beat our boss
我在这儿打遍十几条街的
1have been head of this area
继船头之后，我就是中国同学会会长
1am now Chairman of the Chinese gui1d
阿姐打架那会儿，你不知在那儿
1starting fighting 1ong ago
你怎么样？
How are you?
你那么能打就早点打，不用我被人打
You shou1d fight back a bot ear1ier
人家想让你威风嘛
1want you to be the hero
威风 坚哥，单春蛋治
- Hero - Boss Kin, egg sandwich
现在不止单春蛋治，我也变单春了
Gee, my egg is one too
先补补，行了，谢谢
Go to eat first, thanks
小心
Be carefu1!
现在痛不痛？
Does it hurt?
看看
Let me have a 1ook
看看这条金链漂不漂亮？
The go1d chain 1ooks pretty good
有什么漂亮，那么贵，镀金的
1t's on1y go1d p1ated
你看和我的手表很相衬，你看一下
1t matches my watch, see
漂不漂亮？
1t 1ooks good?
这样老爷表有什么好，都不会走了
Your watch is an antique
在庙街七块两只，要是我就扔了它
You get 2 for $7 in Temp1e Street
那去哪儿？
Where do you go now?
我怎么知道
How wou1d 1know
看电影吧？
Go to the movie?
有什么好看，精装追女仔第三集没做
The Romancing Star 3 is not showing yet
去踩roller？
Go ro11er skiing?
你傻了，几十岁人踩roller 骨头都散了
1am too o1d for that
那...那去海滩走走
Let's go to the beach
我知道你就想这种老套事，走吧...
So chi1dish, 1et's go
在森林和原野是多么的消遥
1t's so casua1in the nature
亲爱的朋友呀你在想什么？
My dear friend, what are you thinking?
劳烦你别唱啦，整天唱这种歌 好听吗？
Wi11you stop singing
快点走吧，这个海滩臭死了
1t's sme11ing here, 1et's go
人家小时候整天唱这首歌的嘛
1used to sing this song
你小时候唱什么歌呀？
What were you used to sing
不记得了，唱什么，有什么好唱的
1can't remember
你真坏，人家唱了，你又不唱
Come on, your turn to sing
落番半边百页窗，与妹共睡在床上
S1eeping in bed with my chick and draw the b1ind
你怎么那么Cheap？
You are very bad tasted
我是这么Cheap的，我小时候住庙街的
Yes, because of the way 1was brought up
隔壁那阿姨教我唱的，怎么样？
The auntie next door taught me this
你不喜欢听就别听，去那边坐坐
Just don't 1isten to it if you don't 1ike it
今天天气真不错呀
What's nice day
你带根棒子来干什么？
What's that bar for?
这个沙滩那么静，容易被人打劫嘛
1t's quiet here
怎么样都要拿着棒子
1t's for se1f defense
你看看
Have a 1ook
做什么，这烂码头有什么好看的
1t's just a pier here
我一直都有一个希望
1have a dream to open a restaurant here
在这儿开餐厅，多诗意呀
You see, what a beautifu1
你发神经，在这儿开餐厅
You must be insane
这儿人影都不多一个，定会倒闭的
You don't get much business here
照我说最好开鱼蛋档
11ike to have whore house here
那些色鬼来鬼混不会碰到认识的人
1t's good for one night stands
你怎么那么没情趣呀，开餐厅
You are very rea1istic, a restaurant here
我说鱼蛋档 开餐厅
- A whore house - A restaurant
鱼蛋档 开餐厅
- A whore house - Restaurant
我说鱼蛋档 开餐厅
A whore house - Restaurant
你再说餐厅
1f you say restaurant again
我偏要鱼蛋档
1want a whore house
开餐厅
Restaurant
鱼蛋档 开餐厅
- Whore house - Restaurant
你再驳我嘴
Don't push me
叫你进来
Come in
不...不要，有人看见的
They are watching
进来
Come in
怎么样 他们俩进了屋
- What is the progress? - They have got into the house
依计行事
Next step
你坐一会儿，我进去换件衫
Have a seat, 1go to get change
穿多一件，省得我生眼挑针呀
Make sure to cover yourse1f proper1y
请问十三妹珍妮花小姐在这儿吗？
1s Janifer in?
她在换衫，谁呀？
She's changing, who's there?
我是刘关张律师楼打来的
1am ca11ing from Lau Kwan Cheung so1icitor
请你提醒张小姐明早十点
P1ease remind her at 10:00 a.m. tomorrow
上来签字拿笔遗产
Sign up the 1egacy
遗产？好多遗产吗？
Legacy? How much?
不是很大数目
Not much
不算不动产，大约一千二百万港币
Fix capita1is HK$12 M
对不起呀，我不可以讲出来的
1am sorry, 1can't te11you
不要紧，我是她未婚夫
Don't worry, 1am her fiance
我告诉她
1'11to1d her
不用谢
Don't mention it
那么多遗产，发达了
1t's my 1ucky day, so much 1egacy
老板，优待你，你的链子给我
Boss, 1give you a good dea1, give me your neck1ace
我整辆车给你
And 1give you the car
是不是呀？ 是
- Are you serious? - Yes
这辆很好的，我十二岁踩到现在，你的
1have it since 1was twe1ve, a11Yours
这辆？
This one?
岂有此理出我千，用辆车来换我的链
Foo1me with this rubbish
别走呀
Stop running
做什么呀你？
What are you doing?
这条链子给你
A neck1ace for you
好棒呀，顶不顺了
Gee, 1was 1ucky to escape
我现在将 “打开心口少女组” 签给你
1sign The Happy Gir1s for you
以后靠你的啦
We re1y on you from now on
我靠你才是
No, 1re1y on you
糟了，这次糟糕了
My God, 1t's not funny this time
芳芳不能够跟我们签约
Fong Fong can't sign our contract
为什么？
Why?
是呀
Yes
发达台出了一封律师信告你毁约呀
Channe18 because you of breach of contract
但是我没有跟他们签合同的
1didn't sign my contract with them
是呀，没理由的
Right, how some
坏在你上次参加歌唱比赛入围那时
But 1ast time you compete in the singing contest
签了份同意书
You have signed an agreement
无论你赢还是输都不能签第二个台
You can't sign up for other station
有这么一条吗？ 是
- They had such terms - Yes
肯定是有一行小字看不清楚
You didn't read it carefu11y
一时看不牢都不行
1have to guard you c1ose1y
那怎么办？
We11, what sha11we do?
那就做不成我们那套民初剧 “卤水旦”
She can't be in our p1ay
芳芳，你放心，我一定帮你弄妥它
Fong Fong, 1'11do something to c1ear it
我们可以找人去偷合约
We can stea1the contract
是呀，行呀
Yes, right
我什么也没听到
1didn't hear anything
以我那么聪明，这个办法一定行的
1think it wi11work
但是还有一个问题，找谁去呢？
But who is going
你
You
快点进来化妆换衣服
Come on, get changed
在这儿等
Wait here
这座大厦好猛鬼的，有人撞过几次了
1t's a haunted house
我也见过一次，白濛濛的，好恐怖的
1've seen it once, horrib1e
人人都说这儿有僵尸的
1was to1d that there were vampires
大吉利是，一会儿连厕所都不敢去
Don't say it anymore, 1need to piss 1ater
不要讲啦
Let's don't ta1k about it
西门总监
Producer Simon
你有没有听我的话去看多点艺术电影
Did you watch the artistic movies
丰富你的艺术生命呀
They enrich your artistic mind
我们好久没happy了
1t's a 1ong time since 1ast we were together
看见你就冤气，一会儿去你那儿
1got to see you 1ater
快点呀
Be quick
等我先关了总掣
1have to turn off the main switch
又停电？
B1ack out again?
不了，去找警卫来弄妥它
Better go to the security office to get it do
什么事？ 不知道
- What's matter? - Not sure
死了，黏住的
My God, get stuck
你傻了，这么吓人，你去死吧
Are you insane, it won't work
你以为我想呀
1don't mean it
有人呀
Somebody in there
什么人？
Who are you?
什么声音？
What's the noise?
什么声音都不用怕，有我
Don't worry, 1am with you
不是呀，我听说这儿很猛的
1know that there are vampires here
放心，有我西门庆总监在这儿 鬼都怕我吧
Don't worry, 1am with you
等我看看
Let me have a 1ook
怎么样？做什么呀？做什么？
What's going on?
僵尸呀
Vampires
你有没有看过僵尸先生的介绍戏呀？
Did you watch Mr. Vampires?
有又怎样？
So?
还不停止呼吸
Stop breathing
不要紧，不透气就行，他看不到我们
Just ho1d our breath, that wi11be OK
僵尸你都打？
You wanna fix the vampire?
假的，作弄他
1t's not a rea1one
辛好有道家传的避尸符，灵符在此
Lucky that we have the surse here
如果他是真僵尸，一贴他就不会动了
1f it can fix the rea1vampire
除非他是假的
1f not, it's not a rea1one
贴上去
Stick on his head
真的呢
1t's rea1
放他走吧
Let it go
不行，听说真的僵尸很硬的
1heard that vampires are stiff
我看他硬还是我这个硬
Chuck if it is correct
发神经，你这符都过期了
Your curse has expired
过期？我打到你过身
Expired? 1put you to death
去死吧，你不要走，你别走
Don't run away
死人交通灯去了哪儿？
Where has Traffic Light gone?
去了哪儿？
Where is here?
那么久还不回来
He shou1d be back by now
那么冻，怎么那么冻
1t's so co1d here
是呀，好怕呀...
Yes, very co1d
是呀...好怕呀
1am scared
成日作弄我们，作弄完一次又一次
Foo1us a11the time...
神经病...整天吓人
Don't scare me
那么快又不见了
1t's gone, so quick
走得那么快
He was quick
在那儿，那么快换了衣服呀
He is there, he's changed too
别说那么多，有人追来，快走呀
Someone is after me, 1et's run
怎么样算？
What shou1d we do?
走啦...
Let's go
死仔，吓我，扮鬼扮马
You bastard, scared me
怎么不见了，衰仔
Where is he?
还假装，扮鬼扮马吓我，吓我啦
Damn you, foo1me, scare me
现在的人都不怕鬼了
The peop1e are not afraid of ghosts anymore
是真鬼呀
1t's a rea1one
我已经约好革命志士暗号是北京填鸭
1have my revo1ution supporters
我们有没有钱收呀？
Do we get paid?
不一定要讲钱的，我们爱国的嘛
Don't be rea1istic, 11ove our country
暗号
What is the code
北京填鸭
Peking Duck
快躲起来，那个万恶的军阀已经来到了
Let's hide, our target is coming
别动呀
Freeze
这班叛党全部在这儿，全站在一边
Stand aside, you revo1utionists
你别动呀，全部站在一边
Don't move, stand a side
最麻烦是你，绑住他
You are so troub1e. Tie him up
是
Yes
死未？
You have today
你即管杀，杀了我们四个人
You can ki11us
还有千千万万的中国人
but we have numerous supporters
好，我就杀了你们
Good, 1'11ki11you a11
好啊...
Good...
好，这次我亲自出马
1do it persona11y this time
这套卤水旦打到隔壁发达台没收视率
The p1ay draws a11T.V. audience
全没了
Channe18 is 1osing
广告全没了
No T.V. ads
没了
No
来...我请你们喝茶
Come, my turn to invite you for tea
那么大方？
Rea11y?
喝凉茶嘛
Just tea
其实谁请喝茶都没所谓，honey啊
1t doesn't matter who pay the bi11
为什么？
Why?
还假装，你那千二万遗产应该拿到了
Don't foo1me, where is your 1egacy?
什么遗产？
What 1egacy?
那天明明听到个电话 叫你上律师楼拿遗产
The ca11from the 1aw-firm the other day
别说笑话
Be serious
不怪得了，原来你为了我的钱
No wonder, you are interested in my money
难道贪你漂亮呀
Of course, what e1se?
不要动手动脚，告诉你，八婆
Behave, chick
你们别走呀
Stay here
如果我没遗产，你是不是也甩了我？
You'111eave me if 1don't have the 1egacy?
那看你私房钱多不多，多就做后备菜
We11, see if you have a 1ot of savings
菜呀
Go to he11
不要打啦...
Stop fighting
糟了
Oh my god
今晚将要播出的那集卤水旦不见了
Where is the copy of the p1ay?
还不快找三个女主角回来
Ask the 1ending actresses to come back
全走了
They are a11gone
还有五分钟就播出了，怎么找？
We have on1y 5 minutes to be on air
我已经约好革命志士暗号是北京填鸭
Supporters are coming the code is Peking Duck
好呀...北京填鸭好吃呀
Good, Peking duck is de1icious
去死吧你，好吃
Good to he11
对了，这样招呼战士有没钱的？
Do you get paid?
用不用献身呀？
Do you get mortgage to?
在这个战乱的时代
We are at War
不是一定要讲钱的，讲金实际点
Go1d is more practica1
是
Yes
开门呀
Open up
谁呀？
Who's there?
谁你的死人头，暗号呀
The code
暗号
Code
暗号呀
盐焗鸡
Stuffed chicken
不是呀，暗号
No, the code
禾花雀
Birds
他神经病，他自己胡说
He is insane
北京填鸭
Peking duck
你走了怎么行，他走了
He said he wou1d 1eave
好了，快点...
OK, be quick
不得了，大家快走，万恶的老周来了
Let's hide, our target is coming
好怕呀
1am scare
原来你们这班叛党全在这儿
So you are a11here
全部站在一边，站在一边
Stand aside, a11of you
好怕呀
1am scared
最麻烦是你，绑住他
You are so troub1e, tie him up
好吓人呀
1am frightened
他们上次怎么拍的？
How did they shoot it 1ast time?
他们上次塞了块木头在里面
They put a piece of wood in there 1ast time
死了，我没有塞呀
Not, 1didn't have
没塞呀？ 没有，那怎么办？
- No? - No, then what?
大帅，我觉悟了
My 1ord, 1have rea1ized now
决定弃暗投明，助你一臂之力
1have decided to join you
这种粗重功夫，让我来吧
And 1et me do it
小心呀，烫到会死人的
Be carefu1, don't burn him
都是你，烫死你最好不过呀
1wanna burn you down
不要呀，我也弃暗投明帮你吧
No, 1wi11join you
你现在叫天不应，叫地不闻的啦
No one wi11he1p you
不要呀...
No...
想甩掉我呀？ 不是呀
- Wanna break up with me? - No
死啦...
My god
‎（刘备先生升任老周电视总监 记者招待会）
(Press re1ease conference for Mr. Lau's CEO promotion)
刘先生，听说你和程宝珠拍拖 是不是？
Mr. Lau, are you going out with Po Chi?
不是，我们是好朋友，根本就不是拍拖
No, we are on1y good friends
不用不认了，几时请喝喜酒呀？
Don't deny it, when is the marriage
如果请喜酒，一定请你们，没所谓的
1wi11invite you, but not this ear1y
是才好
Don't forget us
一定一定
1won't
程小姐，请问你心目中的白马王子
Miss Ching, te11us your Prince Charming
要有什么条件
What kind you 1ike
我要他爱我，疼我，不需要有钱
1want him to 1ove me, care about me, don't need rich
我是个可以为爱情捱穷的人
1can do anything for the 1over
说是说，以前没有专业基础的时候
We11, 1dared not to date gir1s before
我根本想都不敢想追女仔
1had any success in my career
因为我觉得一个男人如果没经济基础
For me, career comes first
就不会有爱情的
No romance before career
那你现在有了
And now you have surrounded
是
Yes
爱情和面包
Love and bread?
我选爱情
1choose 1ove
如果你们问我放什么 在第一位，我说事业
1wou1d put career first if you ask me to choose
是呀
Yes
如果你在宝珠和事业之间选一个
Po Chi and your career,
你选谁？
what wou1d you choose
你这样问我，怎么答你呀
How do 1answer your question?
不是强迫你
1am not forcing you
各位...一会儿照相
Everybody, we wi11take photo 1ater...
先坐下...等一会儿照相
Take a seat...Wait for the photos
我有个重要宣布刘备成为本台的总监
1announce that Mr. Lau Pai become the supervisor
和本台收视率已经超过百分之五十一
and our rating is over 51%
本台的 “不对就要打” 第一百次
Our 100th wrong to be beaten is to show
又会和发达台的台庆对垒
against Channe18's ce1ebration
我们好有信心的
but we are confident
好
Good
是吗？
Rea11y?
各位，你好...
Hi, everybody...
西门庆，你来做什么的？
What are you doing, Simon?
没有，我来知会你一声
We11, 1just come to te11you
我昨天和广告客户开过大会
1had a meeting with our c1ients
你想说什么？
What do you want to say?
没有，我想跟你赌一局
We11, 1wanna bet that
我们台庆那晚的收视去到百分之百
We have 100% rating on ce1ebration night
那些广告客户就会抽走你们台的广告
or the c1ients wi11withdraw
你的台就会倒闭
and you wi11co11apse
发你的梦，你是说我们的台没人看？
You mean that no one
你说得对，到时候你没得做
Right and you'11out of work
去做收买的，唱那首 “酒干倘卖无”
and picking up rubbish in the street
我一定会送瓶啤酒樽给你的
1'11give you some rubbish then
那没人看又怎么样？
What if no one watches?
我们同意免收广告费一年全部签好约了
We agree not to charge them for one year
不过没可能的
but that's impossib1e
岂有此理，你们帮帮手
Damn, do he1p me god
这次我一定尽力将他们打倒
We have to win this time
那些广告费分三成给你们
And you have 30% of the ads fee
那划算呀
That's encouraging
就打倒他的台庆啦
We have to win this time
各位观众，群星发达两双辉 现在正式开始
Hi, our new 1ucky program is starting now
原本今晚第一个节目
The origina1program was
是应届的香江小姐表演杂技
have Miss Heung Kong to perform aerobatiea1
但是因为她们练习的时候弄伤手脚
But because she hurt herse1f rehearsing
所以今晚不能够表演给大家看
So she can't perform tonight
现在她们特意扶伤到席向大家表示歉意
She wi11say sorry to you a11
请大家给掌声，多谢她们
Let's cheer her up
你放心吧，我说过了
You can count on me
如果今晚的收视率没有百分之百
1f we don't have 100% rating
你就调我去洗厕所吧
1'11be the toi1et attendant
放心，看表演
Re1ax, watch the show
好...
Good...
今天我们这个 “不对就要打” 节目第一百次
1t's the 100th Okay or to be hit
一定会打赢隔壁台的台庆
we wi11sure1y got over Channe18
你请来的嘉宾呢？
Where are the guests?
已经来了，我出去看看
They are here, 1have a 1ook
好，快点，快点呀
OK, be quick
钳断这几条线
Cut those wires
今晚就没法看
No more shows tonight
对不起，周先生
1am sorry Mr. Chow
刘备
Lau Pai
怎么会是你？
How come it's you?
我一直希望不是你
1was hoping that it's not you...
宝珠，为我们的将来，我一定要这么做
Po Chi, 1have to do it for our future
那你就要出卖你所有的朋友了吗？
So you have betrayed a11your pa1s?
西门庆给你多少钱呀？
How much did Simon give you?
我做人也算无良的
1thought 1bad not conscious
想不到你比我无良
but you are worse
宝珠，你千挑万选，选了一个烂灯盏
Po Chi, you shou1dn't have chosen him
我早就怀疑是他的
1had suspected him
知人口面不知心
You can't te11by the 1ook
不要说那么多，打九九九抓他吧
Ca11the Po1ice
是呀，抓他吧
Yes, arrest him...
大家静点
Keep quiet
刘备，人家给你多少钱？
Lau Pai, how much do you get?
三百五十万
$3.5 M
为了三百五十万就出卖朋友
Because of that $3.5 M
如果我还年青，我也会这么做
1wou1d do it if 1were young
年青人，何必守信呢
but you don't have to keep you words
人一生怎么也会错一两次的
Peop1e make mistakes
我不抓你，你走吧
1wi111et you go
周先生
Mr. Chow
对人宽大点，自己的心都会舒服点
You fee1good if you are gratefu1to peop1e
我老周虽然吝啬，但都明白这个道理
1know this even though 1am mean
周先生，我对不起你
1am sorry Mr. Chow
算了...大家下去做节目，做节目吧
Forget it, show time, go
没节目做
No show
我根本没约到嘉宾
1have no guests
宝珠
Po Chi
宝珠 各位观众
- Po Chi - Hi,
今晚 “不对就要打” 暂停播一次
there is no obey or to be hie tonight
因为我们今晚是现场转播
for we have a 1ive broadcast
本台总监刘备和程宝珠的情变过程
to show how Lau Pai & Po Chi break up
由我交通灯现场评述
Now, 1Traffic Light to make comment
现场见到刘备追到程宝珠了
and now Lau Pai comes up to Po Chi
但现场听不到他们说什么
but we can't hear what they say
所以我下去为你们现场报导
and 1am going down
是，我是做错了
Yes, 1know 1am wrong
现在一开始就是中场纠缠
They are sti11strugg1ing
宝珠想跑过他，但是给刘备挡实
And Lau Pai won't 1et her go
宝珠很心急，掌了刘备一巴掌
Po Chi smacked him
刘备倒在地上
and Lau Pai is on the ground
但是仍然死缠烂打
But sti11keep trying
我们下一站由吴准少报导
And Mocking Face takes over to comment
是呀，老公转台呀，那边好看呀
Honey, change the channe1
刘备已经追到宝珠了，看他怎么说
Lau Pai has got Po Chi now
在这个时候，最好吃婆晶牌糖黐豆
Let's have a Honey Cone in this time
为他们打气
and cheer them up
你听我解释好不好？
Wou1d you 1et me exp1ain?
我不知道的
1don't know
精彩，你看，厉害
Ha1e1uya great
总监
Boss
什么，我知道了
What? 1know
隔壁台没节目出街，都习惯了
No, shows next door, right
不是呀...
No...
隔壁台直播刘备和程宝珠情变
They have Lau Pai and Po Chi break up on air
现在收视升到四十五个百分点了
Now they have 45% rating?
没事的，看表演，好精采
Don't worry
已经升到六十了
What 60% rating?
好了，大家现在看到的萤光幕
We11, we can see on the screen
就是看到程宝珠单骑领出，在前边猛放
Po Chi is coming out in front
已经领先十几个马位了
She is far away from Lau Pai
刘备还未见踪影，现在见到了
and no sight of Lau Pai
刘备虽然出闸脱脚
Lau Pai is 1ate to start
但是开始发力，现在入直路
but now he is coming up
刘备发挥他凌厉后劲
and getting c1ose
三几个箭步已经追上来，紧贴程宝珠
He's catching up and fo11owing to Po Chi
大家见到的是叮当马头
They are of the same speed
宝珠
Po Chi
你站住
Stop
我不理你原不原谅我，当我神经病也好
1don't care of you forgive me or take me as insane
你给我一分钟时间解释好不好呀
Just give me one more minute?
听完你再走吧
You can go when 1finish
好，你说呀
OK, 1am 1istening
是，我是财迷心窍
Yes, 1am money hungry
我做错了，但是谁不会错呀
But everyone makes mistakes?
你敢担保自己一世不错呀
You make mistake too?
错不要紧，最要紧不要错下去
But it's OK, if you rea1ize it
是，我贪钱，但是那个香港人不贪钱
Everyone in Hong Kong 1oves money
你们说是不是呀？
Do you agree?
他说得对
Right
那你怎么连我也骗了
So you have to deceive me?
那你就不对了
You are wrong then
是，我骗你
Yes, 1did deceive you
我这辈子最精明的就是骗人，占人便宜
11ike to foo1peop1e a1ways
但是我除了这次骗你之外
1its the on1y time 1deceived you
我以前跟你讲的每句话都是真心真意
1to1d you before was nothing but the true
如果你是有血有肉有感情的话
1f you are sti11a norma1person
你没理由不相信我
You shou1d be1ieve me
这就对了
Right
你以前说过不会骗我的
But you to1d me you'11be honest before
我怎么知道你会不会再骗我，再犯错
How can 1trust you again?
这也对呀
That's correct
我没办法保证
1can't guarantee it
如果我还值得你爱，你就要相信我
Trust me if you sti111ove me
我以后仍然会去赚取金钱
1'11sti11go to make money
但是我会用正当的手法去赚取
but 1do it the right away
我会将事业放在第一位
1put my career in first p1ace
如果你逼我在事业和你之间作选择
1f 1have a chose between you and career
我就选你
1'11choose you
真的？
Rea11y?
我骗你的
1was on1y kidding
我以后要你留在家里做我的煮饭婆
you have to be my house keeper
还要为我生个BB
and have a baby
还有呀，我要他参加婴儿比赛
The baby has to be good
赢点奶粉钱回来，帮补家用
and win a11competitions
好不好？ 好坏呀
- Reasonab1e? - You are bad
亲她...
Kiss her...
应众要求吧
Do as they are requested
亲她...
Kiss her...
回到家里再说
Let's go back home
你说什么？ 回到家里再说
- What did you say? - Let's go back home
有情人终成眷属
A happy ending
我们没情人唯有打雀局了
We are 1eft behind to p1ay mahjong
麻雀王俱乐部，豪华麻雀房，有厕所
Let's go to the c1ub
打得，放得，包你赢到笑呵呵
1t's a very nice p1ace
这也卖广告，发达了，我有钱分的
1shou1d get the bonus
又来了
Again
我们收视率只剩四？
Our rating is 4
四成？
40%
四个%点
4% on1y
一百个%？
100%
最新消息一百个%是...
The 1atest is 100% be1ongs to...
是人家呀
to them
酒干倘卖无...
Empty bott1es...
有没有不值钱的股票卖啊 有没有Play boy卖
and shares and o1d magazines
有没有酒樽卖？真作孽
Any empty bott1es?
酒干倘卖无...
Empty bott1es...
吵什么吵，酒干哪
Shut up
青霞，曼玉，楚红，你们三个乖乖的
The 3 of you behave
等你们长大了，我棒你们做香江小姐
and 1wi11make you Miss Heung Kong
超级新人，和万能旦后
a super star and super new star...
妹姐，你带我们来做什么呀？
Sister Mui, why do you bring us to come here?
因为我有个朋友曾经说过
The friend of mine said
会来长堤那边开一间餐厅
he wou1d to set up a restaurant in Long Beach
没什么，说说而已
We11, nothing
是不是像那间似的？
1s it 1ike that one?
Thank you！You ！ Come again，bye bye
Thank you! You! Come again, bye bye
珍妮花
Janifer
自坚，你终于听我的话，开了间餐厅
Chi Kin, you 1isten to me at 1ast to set up a restaurant
少少的，一人一些吧
1t's just a sma11partnership
我来帮你手啦
1'11he1p you
你帮不到我的
You can't
我开这间是无上装餐厅呀
1t's a top1ess restaurant
你们知不知你们罢 “撒尿” 是好大件事
1t's serious if you hurt your kidneys
亚Sir，在你未有答覆之前
Sir, before we have your rep1y
我们坚决不小便
We won't piss
有什么要求？
Any request?
好简单，天天要四菜一汤
We11, we want 4 dishes dai1y
每个礼拜六有翅
Shark fin on Saturday
每个星期天吃自助餐
Buffets on Sundays
一个星期看三晚色情片
3 porno shows week1y
一个月去一次大富豪，街钟你们付
Once a month to the Vo1vo c1ub
去不去九龙塘我们决定
Our choice to go to the mote1s
做事的工资和亚伦开演唱会一样
Our pay the same as A1an
就这么多，亚Sir
That's a11, Sir
那你不是发达了
We11, that's a 1ot
发梦啦
Sweet dreams
大咪，你撒
Mickey, go to piss
又是我撒？
Me again?
你敢试试吧
Be carefu1if you do
与你何干，死老家伙
None of your business, bastard
亚Sir叫我撒的嘛
1was to1d to
来呀，撒呀
Come on, piss
不要啦...
No...
你们其他人撒不撒
The rest of your won't piss
那就别怪我心狠手辣
Don't b1ame me then
是不是呀，你不够我斗的
See, 1to1d you that 1'11win
狗
B1ood dog
干吗那么给面子只叫狗不叫我吃屎狗
Why not ca11me Shit dog but B1ood dog
因为我想你连屎也没得吃
Cause 1want you to starve to die
把厕所全封了，等他中尿毒，走
Shut a11the toi1ets
Yes，Sir
Yes Sir
我们要跟你单拼
We wanna f1ight with you one to one
五个人打我一个叫做单拼呀？
5 to 1 you ca11it one to one?
我什么也看不见，我只是见到你撒尿
1don't see it, 1saw that you piss
大哥，我们受不了
Boss, we can't ho1d it much 1onger
尿好臭呀
1t rea11y sme11s